clearcapital.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Clear Capital

ClearCapital.com, Inc. (“Clear Capital®“), including its affiliates:

1\. Collects non-public personal information (any information that can be used to distinguish or trace your identity) about you from the following sources  
    a. From applications or other forms we receive from you or your authorized representatives;  
    b. From transactions with, or from the services being performed by, us, our affiliates, or others;  
    c. From our internet web sites;  
    d. From the public records maintained by governmental entities; and  
    e. From consumer or other reporting agencies;

2\. Collects and uses the following types of non-public personal information in compliance with applicable legal requirements:  
    a. Personal data such as first name, last name;  
    b. Contact data such as email address, telephone number, and physical/mailing address;  
    c. Financial account information (only in limited circumstances);  
    d. Usage and technical data, including information on how and when you visit our website such as IP addresses, browsing history from our website, etc.; and  
    e. Other personal information that may be necessary to provide products or services to you;

3\. Does not disclose any non-public personal information about you except:  
    a. to agents, independent contractors or representatives to provide you with requested services;  
    b. to third-party contractors or service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf;  
    c. to law enforcement or regulatory officials when applicable law or regulations require us to do so;  
    d. where required by law or judicial process (such as a court order);  
    e. to other parties with appropriate consent; or  
    f. otherwise to the extent permitted under federal or state privacy laws;

4\. Restricts access to non-public personal information to employees who need to know that information to provide services to clients; 

5\. Maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard non-public personal information;

6\. Does not collect non-public personal information from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13) without permission from a parent or guardian. Clear Capital websites are meant for adults and are not intended or designed to attract persons under the age of eighteen (18); 

7\. Are not responsible for the protection or privacy of any information you provide when visiting a link on our website to another website we do not control. You should read the privacy policy of any website you visit; and

8\. Relies on “cookies” (small file sent to your computer through your browser) to help with your user experience when visiting our website. You can choose to accept or decline cookies, but remember that if you decline cookies, it may impact your user experience on our website. Our website does not respond to “Do Not Track” requests enabled through your browser.  

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

If you have questions regarding this policy, or otherwise wish to correct any information with us, please contact Clear Capital at:

ClearCapital.com, Inc.  
Attn: General Counsel  
10266 Truckee Airport Road  
Truckee, CA 96161  
530.550.2500
